you guys are fun i got to get out of
here and uh
before i do and i know this is dry bar
and i'm a big fan of it and i'm a big
fan of you guys for supporting it um and
i know you guys want the big comedy
laugh at the at the very end and uh
you know but when my wife was in um in
delivery i was thinking about a lot of
things because i was seeing my whole
life change right before my eyes
and uh you know we binge watched a show
um about bullying in high school and it
really brought back a lot of bad
memories
and uh i guess it reminded me all the
things that i hated it reminded me all
the things that i don't want for my son
but during that time it also reminded me
of the moment i truly knew my wife was
the one for me
it was about four years ago around this
time and you know on facebook how the
the things pop up like the event pages i
saw the words 10-year high school
reunion
and i told my wife what i wanted to do
and at this time we're not even engaged
she's still my girlfriend she's like i
love you and i'll support you in this
so we go to the restaurant where they're
having the reunion and as soon as i walk
in the doors i locked eyes with the most
popular guy
if you didn't go to this high school you
just know he's the most popular guy he
had like 15 people listening every word
he had to say he had a nice shoes nice
clothes nice haircut
i was telling my wife by the hand i let
go i take a deep breath and i walk right
over to him and i put my finger in his
chest i was like you made my life
miserable it has finally taken me after
10 years to accept me for who i am i
took what your opinion was of me as fact
and that's not right
you no longer have this control over me
and every one of you who's listening to
this guy you should be disappointed in
yourselves and you should know better
and i turn around i grab my wife by the
hand we walk out we're not even there
for five minutes
we get to the car i open up the car door
for her she sits down i shut it as i'm
walking around to the front my knees
start to shake and i have to hold myself
up on the hood of the car so i can walk
i get in the front door i sit down and
as i go put the key in the ignition my
hands are shaking really bad and i drop
the keys between the seats
and at this point i'm hysterical i'm
shaking i'm sweating i'm starting to
swear i'm starting to cry and as i'm
just just this ugly mess my wife just
puts her hand on my knee and i look up
at her and she's giving me the biggest
smile and she tells me how proud of me
of how i made her and how much she loves
me
and my wife's smile has always made me
smile
so even though in this hysterical mess i
i'm smiling
after about a minute i start to calm
down and that smiling turns into
laughter like big belly laughter
and they were laughing so hard we're
crying
because i never went to that high school
[Laughter]
we did that schtick for the next 10
weeks
you're real happy costello thank you
guys so much my name is dan
are brown
[Music]
you